{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_15_3LS24X",
                "player_4_3LS24X",
                "player_1_3LS24X",
                "player_10_3LS24X",
                "player_5_3LS24X"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                15,
                4,
                1,
                10,
                5
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "liedown",
                "stand",
                "stand",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    274.394,
                    4133.31,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    -133.43757063561617,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    786.692,
                    3027.27,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    116.44917124459988,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    567.139,
                    3700.049,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    88.68249224882112,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    550.761,
                    3908.786,
                    81.924,
                    0,
                    33.64246001467217,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    453.369,
                    4016.989,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    -169.88201220412836,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            721.804,
            3223.367,
            82.097
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1213.988151483537
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            939.022,
            2772.854,
            82.097,
            0,
            112.73745513459947,
            0
        ],
        [
            1094.142,
            3870.599,
            100.865,
            0,
            -168.7110317164304,
            0
        ],
        [
            -27.774,
            2573.281,
            -154.806,
            0,
            64.91512277689034,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many human figures are in a standing position?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many men are identified in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are bald?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Among the men in the scene, how many are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many women in the scene have a light skin color and are not bald?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many men in the scene are not bald?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in the brown sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. lying down"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouching",
                    "B. kneeling",
                    "C. standing",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "C. standing"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. standing"
                ],
                "answer": "D. standing"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. leaning"
                ],
                "answer": "B. lying down"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the bald man in a brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in a floral shirt relative to the bald man in a brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the back of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in a brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in a burgundy polo and light pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in a floral shirt relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in a brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in a burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the man in a burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in a camo vest relative to the man in a burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}